(Leonard:)I worked hard on
that speech, too.
(Penny:)Oh. You could tell it to me.
(Leonard:)Oh, thank you,
but I'm okay.
(Penny:)Are you sure?
(Penny:)I could pretend I'm a
high school cheerleader
(Penny:)who can't control herself
around esteemed alumni.
(Leonard:)Greetings, distinguished
cheerleaders.
Ooh!
(Howard:)Okay, the WiFi extender
is on, the camera's on,
(Howard:)they're both on
the same network;
(Howard:)we should be
getting an image.
(Sheldon:)All I see is a black screen.
(Sheldon:)And my own reflection.
(Sheldon:)I look sad.
(Howard:)Maybe we should
recalibrate it.
(Sheldon:)All right.
Step one:
(Howard:)rapidly flip
the calibration switch
(Howard:)from the fully up
to the fully down positions
(Howard:)for at least ten times.
It actually says "at least"?
(Penny:)Yeah.
Why would they say "at least"?
(Sheldon:)Is it ten toggles?
Is it 100 toggles? You know?
Is it 1,000 toggles?
10,000 toggles?
100,000 toggles?
Sheldon!
(Sheldon:)You see where
I'm going with this.